He's asleep
That one
Don't worry
He's probably just exhausted from playing all day
Tell me the truth
You already know everything
Hey, beautiful
Can I ask you for a favor?
What is it?
Take him away
Whether he agrees or not
You know what?
Blue Kexing
was originally an interstellar nomadic civilization
Back then, people traveled to different planets
to experience different lives
But because of our fragile physiques
stories like yours and his
kept happening over and over again
Gradually
Blue Kexing people
were forbidden to leave their planet
They could only connect through magnetic fields
to their so-called 'right' person
Over time
the people of Blue Kexing became colder and more indifferent
Turning into beings that only cared about efficiency
and doing what was 'correct'
Thank you, Qi Miao
You allowed Hao Ruichi to experience
something that could never be found on Blue Kexing
I will take him away
Whether he agrees or not
Every story must come to an end
What about Qi Miao?
She's gone
She said she doesn't want to go through another farewell
Hao Ruichi
Qi Miao was brave
She has already made her final decision
Don't let her down
Qi Miao asked me to relay a few words to you
She said
With you gone
Three meals a day
And the four seasons of a year
She will live her life just as you hoped,
loving life,
taking good care of herself.
From now on,
she will be her own lucky star.
And,
when you go back,
she will also meet the right person,
and start a new life.
Qi Miao,
I never expected that,
after writing so many melodramatic plots,
one would actually happen to me.
Qi Miao,
I have something to do today,
so I won't be seeing you off.
But if you ever come back,
I will be there to welcome you,
come rain or shine.
If you,
I'm here to tell you,
after going back,
I will fulfill my duties as a Star Messenger properly.
I will listen to you,
and live life well.
Not for another meeting or reunion,
Goodbye,
Hao Ruichi.
Qi Miao.
Elite,
you ate the Blueka Fruit,
letting you live decades on Earth.
Live well,
and forget Blueka Star.
Goodbye,
dear brother.
Don't worry,
Miaomiao has us with her.
Goodbye.
Who would've thought this guy turned out pretty decent.
Goodbye, Hao Piaoliang.
You should know,
though far away, there's someone who's not handsome,
but humorous and charming—Qi Dongdong.
You’ve amazed him for over twenty years,
you are his white moonlight.
So, it was a confession.
It's almost time.
Let's go.
No need to wait anymore.
She's not coming.
Get ready to board.
Hao Ruichi.
What do you like about me?
That's a bit hard to answer.
Come on, just say it.
What do you like about me?
I like the heartbeat I feel every time we kiss.
I like the smile you give me when I act silly.
I like how you share with me
everything—both your joys and your sorrows.
I like you.
You’re so beautiful,
perfect,
and unique.
I enjoy every single minute I spend with you,
even when you don’t say a word.
I like you,
because you make me feel whole.
because you are my friend,
my family,
and my girlfriend.
I love you
because you’re my entire world.
Goodbye,
my lucky star.
Get in the car, sis.
Sis.
Don’t you have a new drama press conference to attend?
Why aren’t you wearing something formal, like a dress?
They care about my work,
not my clothes.
Sis, let me tell you something.
As a single woman,
you should dress up a bit.
Otherwise, you might never find someone to marry.
Alright, alright,
I get it.
Boss Qi,
send me the press conference address.
Wait a moment.
We’re going somewhere else first.
What are you doing?
What's wrong?
You scared me!
Why are you making such a fuss?
Who told you to mess with that?
Didn't I tell you not to touch anything?
Is it that serious?
I was just tidying up the table.
I was just worried you might be too busy.
Too busy with what?
I've managed battleships with thousands of crew before.
How hard could it be to run a small restaurant?
Yes, yes, you're the best.
You're amazing.
Eit.
Have you decided on a name for the baby yet?
I've thought it through,
Let's call it Ai, it's simple,
How about that?
What kind of nonsense is that?
Doesn't it sound good?
Then let's call it Ai: A Ray of Light.
Ai Yi Te, Ai Yi Te.
I usually tell you to read more books,
What on earth are you even coming up with?
Not nice to hear either.
Got it.
Then let's call it 'Ai's Delicious'.
It perfectly suits our careers.
The name doesn’t matter.
As long as the baby doesn’t end up as silly as you.
I’m not silly!
Young lady.
Long time no see.
Boss.
Do you still remember me?
Of course.
You are our 1,000th customer.
Why isn't your partner here today?
He...
He went on a business trip far away.
Then get a bowl of snail noodles.
No, thanks.
I have something to do today.
What could be more important than eating?
You know,
don’t just rush through life.
Enjoy it.
Have a seat.
It'll be ready soon.
Boss,
Get me a bowl too.